Guide to the Kate Bornstein papers 1910-2018
Brown University Library
- Digital materials
  - 3-2 Borderline, Beta 1.pages
  - 3-2.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life - 2.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  - 3-4 Where It Gets Complicated V2.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st hackjob.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated 1st merge.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated.pages
  - 3-4 where it gets complicated-tighter.pages
  - avb_obit.pages
  - eulogy for my brother.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5 - 2.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5 - 3.pages
  - Book 2 Chapter 5.pages
  - how the sea org made a man out of me.pages
  - text to grab for so made a man.pages
  - 3-1 Alpha Draft In Progress.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 1.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 1-5.pages
  - 3-1 Beta 2.pages
  - 3-5 Everybody Else's Girl Beta 1.0.pages
  - 3-5 Girl, After Hard Copy Edit Beta 2.0.pages
  - A Queer and Pleasant Mistress.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 kb pass 1.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 (original).pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2 cleanstart.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 2.pages
  - Book 2 Exported From Scrivener.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  - pages compatibility check kb pass 1.pages
  - 3-5 Girl KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.0.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Book 3, 2.1.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 clean.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 3 for Scrivener.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 3 KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 KB pass 2.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Part 3 Redux.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie—Gold.pages
  - Queer and Pleasant Danger Part 3 Gold.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 clean.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB pass 2.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  - book 1.pages
  - book 2.pages
  - book 3.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 2.0.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 2 KB pass 3.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2 clean.pages
  - queer and pleasant danger book 1 KB pass 2.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie KB 1st Pass.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  - Text for Cover Proposal 2.pages
  - Text for Cover Proposal.pages
  - book-spine.pages
  - Queer Pleasant Book Cover Beta 1.pages
  - QueerPleasantBookCoverTextPush.pages
  - My Girlfriend Is Becoming The Man Of My Dreams.pages
  - Dixon Place QPD Launch Schedule.pages
  - DixonPlaceQPDlaunchFlier.pages
  - Kate Bornstein, Book Release Event-May 1st, 120406.pages
  - KBDixonPlaceLaunchPressRelease.pages
  - QueerAndPleasantLaunchProgram.pages
  - climbing the foremast.pages
  - Coming Out.pages
  - molly asks me to marry her.pages
  - My Virginity.pages
  - BILD Interview.pages
  - A Queer And Pleasant Danger Pre Copy Edit.pages
  - letter to jess.pages
  - cover letter to page proof corrections.pages
  - QPD Page Proof Attachments.pages
  - Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  - KB_AuthorPublicity&Marketing.pages
  - A Queer And Pleasant Danger.pages
  - QueerPleasantDanger1_5.pages
  - QueerPleasantDanger_1_5_illustrated.pages
  - Miss G monologue.pages
  - Virtually Yours 2.0.pages
  - Virtually Yours Intro, Beta 1.pages
  - Keynote Champaign-Urbana Pride Festival.pages
  - 3-4 Minutes 4th Annual Womens Awards.pages
  - For the Fun of It Intro 3.0.pages
  - The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  - You Me and Gender BC PASS.pages
  - 20 Questions.pages
  - DIVA questions Pages09.pages
  - Bornstein's Theory of Relativity KB pass Pages 09.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-1.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-2.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-3.pages
  - China Film Text 1st Draft P09.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Final.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote No Restrictions.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-2.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Reader-3.pages
  - Femme Conf 2010 Keynote Sync.pages
  - Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum for blog.pages
  - Keynote Women-Gender Consoritum.pages
  - Play List for @largeheartedboy.pages
  - Power of Femme Marist Conf Keynote.pages
  - KB_OpEd_Aug2014_Pages_09.pages
  - KB_OpEd_Aug2014-2.pages
  - CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - KB final draft CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - Genesis Pomo.pages
  - Mitzvah Sabbath KESHET 09.pages
  - NUJLS Mitzvah Text.pages
  - Talk at Vigil Against Hate Crimes Xavier 09.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for Neherim.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for RRC 2012.pages
  - Welcome to NYU LGBTQ.pages
  - Description.pages
  - Supplies.pages
  - KB Photo Assortment 2011.pages
  - KB-Career-Summary-2010.pages
  - Author Questionnaire by Kate Bornstein.pages
  - *GSMS Foreword by BC—KB pass.pages
  - B survey letter pages 09.pages
  - BC to Donia Finders Fees Smackdown.pages
  - Figments of Erotic Imagination-KB Pass.pages
  - New BDSM Chapter—KB Pass.pages
  - New EAM for T&GNC People Chapter KB pass.pages
  - New Introduction copy KB pass.pages
  - New Safer Sex section—KB PASS.pages
  - Orgasms with Spirit Class #4 KB Pass.pages
  - Trans Survey Draft #2 KB pass pages 09.pages
  - Urban Tantra certificate.pages
  - Chapt. #1-The Ecstatic Experience Vs2.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB 1st Draft.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better KB 2nd pass.pages
  - Rogue femininity.pages
  - Buffalo Night by Caitlin.pages
  - Midnight Bleary.pages
  - David Harrison My experiences on the CSETI Training.pages
  - femme on femme long version.pages
  - My White Underwear Story.pages
  - JVB Interview.pages
  - A.Mc.Q.201120.pages
  - Princess book proposal.pages
  - Princess Proposal 2.0.pages
  - Antig-Lines.pages
  - GoFundMe Comments.pages
  - Kate Stay Alive.pages
  - Talking Points B's Ecstasy Hour.pages
  - short talk performance & workshop descriptions.pages
  - NYSAF.F TO M.Kate Bornstein (Dr. Shelton).pages
  - An addendum to house sit.pages
  - House-Sitter Factoids.pages
  - Quotes About KB.pages
  - 09-10 newsletter.pages
  - Kate Bornstein One Sheet.pages
  - 10-11 newsletter.pages
  - 13-14 newsletter.pages
  - catalogue essay 13-14.pages
  - some text for 13-14 cat.pages
  - MWRU Director Script La Mama 2017.pages
  - MWRU Performance Script 2016 PO9.pages
  - Backup of Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  - Talking Points Post-Trans March.pages
  - Talking Points Pre-Trans March.pages
  - 100 GLBT Colleges Contact Info.pages
  - FINAL Schedule for Kate Bornstein Visit.pages
  - New Gigs 09 outline.pages
  - KB_Amherst_Details.pages
  - ASU SORC Speaker Template.pages
  - Masque for John #1.pages
  - 09-106 LGBTA 2-11 Speaker.pages
  - kate's itinerary.pages
  - Power Bottoming panel at TES.pages
  - Appearance Agreement Kate Bornstein.pages
  - contract U Miss.pages
  - Kate Bornstein Contract.pages
  - KATE BORNSTEIN schedule.pages
  - Denver-Twin Cities.pages
  - Elon University 041112 itinerary.pages
  - final proposal.pages
  - IC_Kate Bornstein completed.pages
  - University of Toledo 10.16.13 schedule.pages
  - University of Illinois 100212 itinerary.pages
  - University of Florida 102212 itinerary.pages
  - Urbana Trip 0913-20 schedule.pages
  - Bornstein QAF contract 2012.pages
  - Bornstein Rider QAF 2012.pages
  - Kate Bornstein workshop contract.pages
  - WNE_KateB_itinerary.pages
  - KB_Acting_Wkshop_Handout.pages
  - KB-Acting-Wkshop-Handout-2.pages
  - charts for role play.pages
  - Guidepost & Control System Charts.pages
  - Michael Shurtleff 12 Guideposts.pages
  - 2012 Talk to CCSU 3rd Annual Lavender Commencement.pages
  - Carroll University NCOD 2010.pages
  - CBST Pride Shabat Talk.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 09.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires 2013.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SASSE 2010.pages
  - Dangerous Dreams Damned Desires SFU 09.pages
  - Hello Cruel Bullies ♀ History 2011.pages
  - KB CBST Pride Shabat 2012.pages
  - Men Women Rest of Us Perf Notes 2012.pages
  - Sex, Bullies, and You 2009.pages
  - Sex, Bullies, and You 2010 Reader.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  - Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  - william paterson piece.pages
  - Anna Story.pages
  - Politics of Desire 1.0.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - Theater, and Future of the Body.pages
  - Man Without a Family Reader.pages
  - Reading with David.pages
  - Carrol Univ Coming Out Day.pages
  - Hidden A Gender.pages
  - The Monologues.pages
  - 316 HouseSit Notes 10:13.pages
  - 316 HouseSit Notes Apr2013 KB.pages
  - do u c p.pages
  - KB Books Amazon Links pages 09.pages
  - aftercare.pages
  - Dear Galley Reader Letter.pages
  - dixon place femme blurb.pages
  - email from pussy.pages
  - KB long bio May 2015 pages09.pages
  - KB pass at TCKB.pages
  - KB Pass.pages
  - memoir-template.pages
  - Pioneer Speaking.pages
  - Questions_for_Switzerland BC Pass.pages
  - Timed Talk—Save This As Template.pages
  - A Plan For Peace Nov 27 92.pages
  - Apartheid of Sex Martine Rothblatt.pages
  - Talk to KC L&G re Brandon Teena May 14 1995.pages
  - An Afternoon of Bridge.pages
  - Backup of Two Forms of ID.pages
  - Circumstances by Design.pages
  - Face In The Mirror.pages
  - Newlyweds.pages
  - Team Spirit.pages
  - Testing a Theory.pages
  - Two Forms of ID.pages
  - 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC 6-11 Cape Cod.pages
  - 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC Aug2011.pages
  - ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  - Lock the DAMN door.pages
  - turn around damn door.pages
  - JJ_Reading.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic 2.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic.pages
  - Scientology New Yorker.pages
  - Scientology Nuts and Bolts.pages
  - call me a cockeyed optimist.pages
  - Chapter 3 Ebook.pages
  - Hard Candy Chapter 3 Reader.pages
  - Bornstein_iphonecontract.pages
  - copy_txt.pages
  - hcw1pg.pages
  - Quotes About KB.pages
  - IRS Collections Letter June 2011.pages
  - letter to irs re payment agreement.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Dec 2011.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Feb 2012.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Jan 2012.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Jul-Aug 2011 copy.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Nov 2011.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Oct 2011.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Sep 2011.pages
  - IRS Payment Letter Sep 2013.pages
  - Letter to NY State re Installment.pages
  - NY State Collection Letter June 2011.pages
  - 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS.pages
  - 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS-2.pages
  - 2006-2009 Ltrs to IRS-3.pages
  - kate at the hospital.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09-2.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09-3.pages
  - kb_medical_history_2010 copy.pages
  - kb_medical_history_2010.pages
  - Letter to Oxford re Deductible Year.pages
  - HOSPITALIZATIONS--SURGERIES .pages
  - Medical Records Request.pages
  - NEW PATIENT QUESTIONNARIE2012.pages
  - Present Physicians--Concurrent Medical Care.pages
  - KB Meds Mar 2013.pages
  - KB Meds Nov 2012 1.pages
  - Affirmations for Docs.pages
  - kate at the hospital.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09-2.pages
  - kb meds sheet 09-3.pages
  - kb_medical_history_2010.pages
  - Letter to Oxford re Deductible Year.pages
  - Ltr to Beth Israel Pathology.pages
  - Treatment Ideas Post Lobectomy.pages
  - Treatment Ideas Post Lobectomy.pages
  - 78C821AE-B13E-48CF-8D9C-135C6D40EA09.pages
  - *GSMS Foreword by BC.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft_BC pass.pages
  - EINecessary Review KB Better BC 2nd pass.pages
  - KB final draft CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - MWRU Performance Script 2016 PO9.pages
  - cover letter to page proof corrections.pages
  - QPD Page Proof Attachments.pages
  - Chelsea Manning Open Letter To-3.pages
  - MNGW Please Read Me First.pages
  - KB_AuthorPublicity&Marketing.pages
  - Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  - Tku Lambda Lit Trans.pages
  - Pet Meds Template 2016.pages
  - For the Fun of It Intro 3.0.pages
  - MWRU Director Script La Mama 2017.pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1) clean.pages
  - China Film Text 1st Draft P09.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for RRC 2012.pages
  - New Introduction copy KB pass.pages
  - Bornstein's Theory of Relativity KB pass Pages 09.pages
  - Post registration form London 2015.pages
  - Dear Galley Reader Letter.pages
  - *GSMS Foreword by BC—KB pass.pages
  - *GSMS Foreword by BC—KB pass.pages
  - Timed Talk—Save This As Template.pages
  - 100 GLBT Colleges Contact Info.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - There and Back Again.pages
  - Gender Is A Wooly Worm 1st Draft 09.pages
  - Questionnaire UTPTP London 2015.pages
  - Intros for Guests JE Party.pages
  - Barbara Carrellas One Sheet Edit.pages
  - Barbara Carrellas One Sheet Edit.pages
  - B survey letter pages 09.pages
  - Orgasms with Spirit Class #4 KB Pass.pages
  - Intro All That Jazz.pages
  - Intro All That Jazz.pages
  - Lock the DAMN door.pages
  - turn around damn door.pages
  - aftercare.pages
  - 3-5 Girl.pages
  - Antig-Lines.pages
  - KB Pass.pages
  - New EAM for T&GNC People Chapter KB pass.pages
  - New BDSM Chapter—KB Pass.pages
  - Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  - Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  - Epilogue-Hello Sweetie Raw.pages
  - JVB Interview.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB 1st Draft.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better Draft.pages
  - Figments of Erotic Imagination-KB Pass.pages
  - GOTNG Triangle Publishing Prize Acceptance Talk.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  - 3-5 Everybody Else's Girl Beta 1.0.pages
  - BC_UT_Sweden_4_Berliners.pages
  - Trans Survey Draft #2 KB pass pages 09.pages
  - CreatingChange2016.kb.workshop.proposal.pages09.pages
  - New What is Tantra Chapter KBpass1.pages
  - The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  - The Same Page BC PASS.pages
  - You Me and Gender BC PASS.pages
  - New Safer Sex section—KB PASS.pages
  - 3-5 Girl, After Hard Copy Edit Beta 2.0.pages
  - 3-5 Girl.pages
  - Author Questionnaire Kate Bornstein.pages
  - KB_AuthorPublicity&Marketing.pages
  - 316 HSESITTER INSTRUC Aug2011.pages
  - 316 HouseSit Notes Apr2013 KB.pages
  - DIVA questions Pages09.pages
  - Ecstasy Is Necessary Review KB Better KB 2nd pass.pages
  - Carroll University NCOD 2010.pages
  - KB Books Amazon Links pages 09.pages
  - KB long bio May 2015 pages09.pages
  - kb letter to the revolution for B.pages
  - TWEETS ETC.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Etc for Neherim.pages
  - BumblingFinal JDM (2).pages
  - Blank.pages
  - Questions_for_Switzerland.pages
  - 316 House-Sitter Notes Apr2013.pages
  - do u c p.pages
  - Beautiful Girls.pages
  - MWRU Performance Script 2017 BC copy.pages
  - MWRU Script La Mama 2017 BC copy.pages
  - kb letter to the revolution for B.pages
  - KATE BORNSTEIN TOUR.pages
  - KB workshop promo .pages
  - KATE BORNSTEIN TOUR.pages
  - KB workshop promo .pages
  - ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  - Seasonal_8.5x11.AddressLabel_centered_6.pages
  - Seasonal_8.5x11.AddressLabel_centered_6-2.pages
  - Ernie 98 card.pages
  - kb half page ad.pages
  - We Three for the Book.pages
  - ePub Best Practices for Pages.pages
  - Lock the DAMN door.pages
  - turn around damn door.pages
  - JJ_Reading.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic 2.pages
  - Repair Return Note Etymotic.pages
  - Scientology New Yorker.pages
  - Scientology Nuts and Bolts.pages
  - call me a cockeyed optimist.pages
  - Chapter 3 Ebook.pages
  - Hard Candy Chapter 3 Reader.pages
  - novotesforbulliescontract.pages
  - kb letter to the revolution for B.pages
  - Barbara Carrellas One Sheet Edit.pages
  - cheap sex with bc 2.pages
  - cheap sex with bc 3.pages
  - cheap sex with bc.pages
  - apology to neighbors.pages
  - Bornstein_letter_4_John_Emigh.pages
  - Justin V PS 122 Tribute.pages
  - KB_Endorses_Yetta_Kurland.pages
  - KB_Ltr_John_Emigh.pages
  - Not Guilty Plea—Bus Ticket.pages
  - Open Letter to Queer Youth Norway.pages
  - Rafe Posey Recc to Brown Grad School.pages
  - TORI LOR to JCHP.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR HRSA-NSP.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR NHSC.pages
  - Aiden Fyre LOR.pages
  - Crystal Letter page two.pages
  - Ltr Recc Crystal Yakacki OHSU.pages
  - KB recc for Laura.pages
  - KB_on_Hate_Crimes_Bill_4PHB.pages
  - Cast List Inherit the Earth.pages
  - Inherit the Earth notebook notes.pages
  - inherit the earth opening.pages
  - 1 KB Edit Chap 2.pages
  - 1 KB Edit TOC thru Chap 1.pages
  - 10 KB Edit Chap 10.pages
  - 11 KB Edit Gnite Gday and Acks.pages
  - 3 KB Edit Chap 3.pages
  - 5 KB Edit Chap 5.pages
  - 6 KB Edit Chap 6.pages
  - 7 KB Edit Chap 7.pages
  - 8 KB Edit Chap 8 copy.pages
  - 9 KB Edit Chap 9.pages
  - Author 1st proof AQs (Chap 3 to End).pages
  - Vested Interests Review.pages
  - Acceptance Speech KESHET 09.pages
  - Open Letter re Marriage Equality.pages
  - Intro All That Jazz.pages
  - Crossed Genres Interview.pages
  - Crossed Genres.pages
  - KateBornsteinRebelCupcake.pages
  - Performance Version Crossed Genres.pages
  - UCD_keynote_BC.pages
  - dvd case insert lana and kar.pages
  - dvd label 4 lana kar.pages
  - GOTNG Triangle Publishing Prize Acceptance Talk.pages
  - Kate Bornstein full clean edit.pages
  - Tku Lambda Lit Trans.pages
  - Dixie Belle June 2011.pages
  - Dixie Belle Reader 2011.pages
  - Sleeping Beauty.pages
  - B's pass_TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  - TOTWK_by_KB_for_OutMag.pages
  - TOTWK_by_KB_OutMag.pages
  - Take Back the City Talk.pages
  - Gender Is A Wooly Worm 1st Draft 09.pages
  - 120502 Baldi GENDER OUTLAW China(2).pages
  - Gender Is A Caterpillar Introduction.pages
  - derby gender essay draft 5.pages
  - Gender Outlaw by Kate Bornstein and S. Bear Bergman.pages
  - gleanersGOTNG.pages
  - gotngdraft 3-Mar-2010.pages
  - gotngdraft 4-Feb-2010.pages
  - gotngdraft 4-Jan-2010.pages
  - Lucia Miel 1st draft KB notes.pages
  - Lucia Miel 1st draft.pages
  - LuMi_2.pages
  - On Men, Women and The Rest of Us AV.pages
  - Outlaws Last Gleaning.pages
  - Roz Second Poem.pages
  - Sassafrass Submission 1.pages
  - She-MaleRisingShawnaVirago.pages
  - HCW_Text_KBpass.pages
  - BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  - Beautiful Girls.pages
  - Brown Anthology Piece Text Bits.pages
  - Brown Piece.pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (edited2).pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1) clean.pages
  - Brown Reader Bornstein (KBPass 1).pages
  - Good Sportsmen.pages
  - GO TNG Blog.pages
  - what does mean mean.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  - Ltr to Design-Copyedit Team.pages
  - MNGW Please Read Me First.pages
  - Put with Pyramid.pages
  - Cautionary Interlude.pages
  - Limericks copy.pages
  - Limericks.pages
  - NWGW_Tweets from HG Pass.pages
  - TWEETS ETC.pages
  - TWEETS_only_kb_1st_sort.pages
  - Acknowledgments Plain.pages
  - Acknowledgements.pages
  - MNGW TOC and Intro.pages
  - 1 MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1 Beta_EW.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 1_sketch.pages
  - Start of the Journey.pages
  - exercise—coalition building.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 9.pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 2.pages
  - Treasure Map 1.pages
  - Kyriarchy Worksheer 2-up.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 3.pages
  - 4 MNGW Chapter 4 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 4.pages
  - 101 working table.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 5.pages
  - 6 MNGW chapter 6 Gold sketch.pages
  - measuring sexuality by.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 6.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6 Sketch.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass.pages
  - MNGW chapter 7 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 7 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Chapter 7.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass.pages
  - 8 MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 8 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 8 sketch.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass copy.pages
  - MNGW chapter 9 Gold sketch.pages
  - MNGW chapter 9 sketch.pages
  - MNGW Old Chapter 8 Beta.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass.pages
  - Old Exercises Where Gender Is.pages
  - BalladOfLittleJo_by_Kate_B.pages
  - best wishes for laura ingraham.pages
  - Tao of Mitzvah Sabbath Boddhisatva.pages
  - Transgender Day Remembrance 09.pages
  - william paterson piece.pages
  - betsey_girls_saved_my_life.pages
  - keynote notes beyond the binary.pages
  - GASP 1.pages
  - Cover Sketch 2 by KB .pages
  - cover sketch.pages
  - MNGW BW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  - MNGW BW w ruby slippers.pages
  - MNGW if it were KBs notebook.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans line art ruby slippers KB note.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers KB note.pages
  - MNGW rainbow anarchy trans ruby slippers.pages
  - MNGW Rainbow w Ruby Slippers.pages
  - MNGW Rainbow w Unicorn.pages
  - rainbow back cover beta 1.pages
  - Author 1st proof AQs (Prelims to Chap 2).pages
  - MNGW As to copy editor Qs January 3.pages
  - MNGW Qs to author December 7.pages
  - MNGW Uncle Stinky Where.pages
  - KB Edits Summary MNGW 2nd Proofs.pages
  - MNGW 1st Printing Errata.pages
  - 0 MNGW TOC & Intro.pages
  - 1 MNGW Chapter 1_KBpass.pages
  - 10 MNGW Chapter 10.pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass (Kate Bornstein's conflicted copy 2012-10-21).pages
  - 2 MNGW Chapter 2 KB Pass.pages
  - 3 MNGW Chapter 3 KB Pass.pages
  - 4 MNGW Chapter 4 KB Pass.pages
  - 5 MNGW Chapter 5 KB pass.pages
  - 6 MNGW_chapter 6_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 6 Sex Sex Sex Changes Accepted.pages
  - 7 MNGW_chapter 7_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 8 MNGW_chapter 8_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - 9 MNGW_chapter 9_KB Pass 7x9.pages
  - MNGW Website Marker Page.pages
  - My Old Gender Workbook MASTER.pages
  - My Old Gender Workbook Working Copy.pages
  - MyGenderWorkbook Update Thoughts.pages
  - raw thank you tweets.pages
  - 01 Welcome to Your Workbook.pages
  - 02 Solving the Gender Puzzle.pages
  - 03 Be All You Can Be, Fuck Your Gender, Love Sex Desire.pages
  - 04 Just Say No.pages
  - 05 Just Say Yes, Zen & Art of Gender Maintenance.pages
  - 06 The Playgrounds.pages
  - 07 Cautionary thru Revolutionary.pages
  - QueerAndPleasantProposal.pages
  - THE Acknowledgments.pages
  - FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass 2.pages
  - FM-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  - MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass.pages
  - MS-BornsteinED - with SL edits—KB Pass2.pages
  - 1st QPD Press Release.pages
  - Blurb Letter Janet Reitman copy.pages
  - Blurb Letter Jeffrey Eugenides.pages
  - Blurb Letter Jenny Boylan.pages
  - Blurb Letter Patti Smith.pages
  - Blurb Letter Samuel Delany copy.pages
  - Letter to Librarian Galley Readers.pages
  - Letter to Media Galley Readers.pages
  - Kate proposal.pages
  - Bornstein Edit Salon 2-2.pages
  - kb contacts for tony o.pages
  - A Queer and Pleasant Danger GOLD.pages
  - Dedication-Acknowledgments.pages
  - Book 2 Chap 4 Family Man.pages
  - Family Man copy.pages
  - Family Man.pages
  - text to grab 4 New York the First Time.pages
  - 0-Introduction.pages
  - 2-4.pages
  - 2-5.pages
  - 2-6.pages
  - 3-1 I Meet Daddy Man to Man.pages
  - 3-2 Borderline.pages
  - 3-3 Stages Of Life.pages
  - 3-4 OK This Is Where It Gets Complicated.pages
  - 3-5 Girl.pages
  - 3-2 after the big cut and paste.pages
  - 3-2 Borderline Old.pages